(Howard:)So you wouldn't want to
have anything on Penny?
(Leonard:)Well, of course not.
(Howard:)So, if I actually
know something right now...
(Howard:)and I do...
(Howard:)...you don't want me
to tell you?
(Amy:)Uh...
Pfft, no.
I'll take that as a "Yes."
(Howard:)She's secretly been moving
your collectibles into storage
(Howard:)a little at a time
and you haven't noticed.
(Leonard:)Are you kidding me?
(Howard:)See, I've known
that for weeks,
(Howard:)but, you know, I waited
till the moment
(Howard:)when it would cause him
the most pain.
(Leonard:)Superman's gone,
my stormtrooper's gone.
(Sheldon:)Your Klingon word-of-the-day
calendar's gone.
I'd say "damn it" in Klingon,
(Leonard:)but that wasn't until
next month.
It's "khoo-vakh."
(Leonard:)Khoo-vakh!
(Leonard:)She took my Where's Waldo.
Well, no, no, he's over there.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah, there he is.